#### Contact

Ali Garden Block A, Street#1, House#2, Faisalabad, Pakistan +923217865510 (Mobile) sajidali2444@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sajidali2444 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills
AJAX
HTML 5
CSS

Languages

English Urdu

# Sajid Ali

Lead Software Engineer, Full stack (.NET | MERN)
Lahore District

## Summary

I'm a passionate and pragmatic software engineer with 10 years of professional experience, specializing in full-stack development using Microsoft Technologies on the backend. Strong in object-oriented analysis and design and experience with a wide range of front-end and back-end frameworks. I can assist in all stages of the software development lifecycle and deliver working software with clean architecture and clean code.

#### Experience

AllZone Tech.
Principal Software Engineer
September 2019 - Present (2 years 4 months)
Lahore, Pakistan

I'm a passionate and pragmatic software engineer with 6 years of professional experience, specializing in full-stack development using Microsoft Technologies on the backend. Strong in object-oriented analysis and design and experience with a wide range of front-end and back-end frameworks. I can assist in all stages of the software development lifecycle and deliver working software with clean architecture and clean code.

Team Solution
Principal Software Engineer
April 2015 - September 2019 (4 years 6 months)
Principal Software Engineer
Software development

eWorx International Software Engineer March 2013 - April 2015 (2 years 2 months) Lahore

Application development using .NET technologies ASP.NET MVC With C#, MSSQL, JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML.

#### **TCAW Global**

Team Lead

January 2011 - March 2013 (2 years 3 months)

Lahore

Applications development using PHP, MySql, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, CSS, HTML.

ShareServe

Software Engineer January 2010 - January 2011 (1 year 1 month)

Software Engineer

## Education

Allama Iqbal Open University
BS(CS) Hon's, Computer Science · (2003 - 2007)